Oh, no, thanks.
I'm going to the mall with Emma.
(Leonard:)The kid got a girl.
(Raj:)Unbelievable.
(Howard:)Did anyone see how he did it?
(Sheldon(to Gablehouser):)Don't worry, I've got this.
(Sheldon(to Gablehouser):)Ladies and gentlemen,
honored daughters...
(Sheldon(to Gablehouser):)...while Mr. Kim,
by virtue of his youth and naiveté...
(Sheldon(to Gablehouser):)...has fallen prey to the inexplicable need
for human contact...
(Sheldon(to Gablehouser):)...let me step in and assure you
that my research will go on uninterrupted.
(Sheldon(to Gablehouser):)And that social relationships
will continue to baffle and repulse me.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
[CLAPPING]
- He's back.
- Yeah, mission accomplished.
(Raj:)Forget the mission. How did that
little yutz get a girl on his own?
(Howard:)I guess times have changed
since we were young.
(Howard:)Smart is the new sexy.
Then why do we go home alone
every night? We're still smart.
(Raj:)Maybe we're too smart.